ubiz.mobi 2018-08-30

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
We are committed to giving you transparency of our privacy practices and control over your data in connection
with Ubiz Services (as defined in Ubiz Terms Of Service).
This Privacy Policy covers Ubiz treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information” ) and other
data that Ubiz gathers when you are accessing Ubiz Services. The Services are not available to individuals who are
younger than 18 years old.
Personal Information
• Personal Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Services
    or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected may include your name, email
    address, phone number, birthday, Twitter and/or Facebook usernames, use information regarding your use of
    our Services, and browser information. We automatically receive your location when you use the Services. We
    use various technologies to determine location, such as location services of the applicable operating system or
    browser and sensor data from your device that may, for example, provide information on nearby Wi-Fi- access
    points and cell towers. The Personal Information you provide is used for such purposes as allowing you to set
    up a user account and profile that can be used to interact with other users through the Services, improving the
    content of the Services, customizing the advertising and content you and your friends see (including Ubiz or
    third-party advertising or content), and communicating with you about specials and new features. Your Services
    account will be associated with your email (and optionally a phone number) and this account will be used for
    all our Services that you use. Information you provide to one of our Services may be used with other Services
    you or your friends use. For example, location information we receive in connection with your use of one of our
    apps may be used to customize the content you and your friends see in another of our apps. We may also draw
    upon this Personal Information in order to adapt the Services of our community to your needs, to research the
    effectiveness of our network and Services, and to develop new tools for the community.
• Information Collected Automatically: When you use the Services, Ubiz automatically receives and records
    information on our server logs from your browser or mobile platform, including your location, IP address,
    browser type, operating information, mobile carrier, device and application IDs, cookie information, and
    the page you requested. We treat this data as non-Personal Information, except where we are required to
    do otherwise under applicable law. Unless otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, Ubiz only uses this data in
    aggregate form. We may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our users, collectively, use
    our Services, so that our partners may also understand how often people use their services and our Services.
Personal Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal
Information to anyone, though, your publicly-available information is available to third parties, and we may provide
it to third parties, by license or otherwise. Together with information on how to change the default user settings
or how to generally remove information, where applicable. Ubiz may share your Personal Information only as
described in this Privacy Policy and related documents.

• Friends: Your friends can see, for example, your location (as described in more detail below), name, email,
    phone number, photo, hometown, mayorships and badges, a list of your friends, plans you write or comment
    on, tips you write, and which Ubiz Services you use. Individuals reading this information may use it or disclose it
    to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge. We therefore urge you to think
    carefully about including any specific information you may deem private in comments, plans or tips or other
    content (location or otherwise) that you create in the Services.
• Businesses, Locations, Events and Brands: One of the key purposes of the Services is to help users learn
    about businesses, locations, events and brands (for example, a TV show, a TV personality, newspaper or a
    consumer good that manages a page on the Service) that are relevant to them, and for these entities to
    provide information about themselves, their locations and events to users, as well as to reward users when
    they visit their location or event through offers and specials. When you check-in to a particular location that is
    a ‘claimed location’ your check-ins are shared with that location in order for it to better provide services to you.
    Additionally, brands may have access to aggregated and anonymous data, such as de-identified check-in data
    (that is, not tied to individual users) of users that like their brand.
• Publicy Available Information, the Ubiz API, and Apps: When you use the Services, certain information
    is public, such as your public user profile information, tips, likes, public photos, lists that you create and
    lists of friends, and may be searchable by search engines and be shared with or disclosed to third parties,
    including through our API to a wide range of users and services. We may also share or disclose aggregated
    and anonymous data, such as de-identified check-in data (that is, not tied to individual users), to third parties,
    including users of our API, for analytical or other purposes.
In addition, use of third party apps developed using our API are subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of
such third party developers. Certain Personal Information may be made available to third party developers if you or
your “friends” use these third party apps. You should review the policies of third party apps and websites to ensure
that you are comfortable with the ways in which they use and disclose the information you share with them. We
do not guarantee that they will follow our rules or our Privacy Policy. Note that your friends will also be able to see
which third party apps that you use.
• Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your
    information with them to provide products or services to you. Our agents do not have any right to use Personal
    Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us, and they provide a comparable level of
    protection for your Personal Information.
Determining and Sharing Location
Determining your location - The Services deal with location, so in order to work, the Services need to know your
location. Whenever you open and use/interact with our apps on your mobile device or go to one of our Sites, we
use the location information from your mobile device or browser (e.g., latitude and longitude) to tailor the Services
experience to your current location (i.e., we’ll show you a list of nearby locations, friends and tips). This information
is NOT shared with others. Also, the Services use your mobile device’s ‘background location’ to provide the
Services, including to send you notifications of tips/friends/plans/interesting things etc. near you. If you have
‘background location’ turned on, the Ubiz app will, from time to time, tell us about your device’s location even if
you are not directly interacting with the application.

Sharing Location with the Ubiz app - Your location data is ONLY shared with others when you proactively decide
to “Log in” on the Ubiz app to tell the Services you’re at a particular place. The location information shared with a
“Log in” is the location information of that place.
Sharing Location with Ubiz app - By default, neighborhood sharing is turned on and your location data, at a
neighborhood level, is shared with your Ubiz friends and is updated from time to time using your background
location.
Services Features
The Services include several features that may allow you to share your information with others. For each of these and
our other features, the information available to friends and others, our default user settings, and how to alter the
default settings, is available in the Privacy FAQs. Please review them carefully. Please remember that if you choose
to provide personal information using certain features of the Services, that information may be available to the wider
Services community, or may be published on our Sites, which is subject to indexing by third party search engines.
Sharing with Partners, in connection with business transfers, and for the protection of Ubiz
and others:
• Our Partners: In addition to the data sharing described above, we enter into relationships with a variety of
    businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, these businesses, provide services to you, sell items
    or provide promotions to you through the Services. In other situations, Ubiz provides services, or sells items
    jointly with these businesses. You can easily recognize when one of these businesses is associated with your
    transaction, and we will share your Personal Information that is related to such transactions with that business.
• Business Transfers: If Ubiz or substantially all of its assets are acquired, or in the unlikely event that Ubiz goes
    out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired
    by a third party.
• Protection of Ubiz and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that
    release is necessary to comply with the law, including laws outside your country of residence; enforce or apply
    our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Ubiz , our employees,
    our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations (including
    outside of your country of residence) for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Email Communications
If you do not want to receive commercial email or other mail from us, please indicate your preference by making a
modification on your account settings page or through the ‘settings’ tab on our website once you’re logged into
the Services. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as notices regarding this
Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Services, and you are responsible for reviewing
such legal notices for changes. We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from Ubiz if your computer
supports this type of program. Ubiz uses this confirmation to help us make emails more interesting and helpful and
improve our service.

Cookies and Similar Technologies
We and our agents use technologies like cookies, pixels, and local storage (like on your browser or device, which
is similar to a cookie but holds more information) on our website, in our emails, and identifiers supplied by app
platform companies within our apps to provide you with a range of products and services. You can control cookies
through your browser settings and other tools. By continuing to use our Services through your computer or mobile
device, you consent to our use of cookies, pixels and local storage in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
We may work with advertisers or other partners and advertising service providers to serve ads or services to
computers, mobile phones or other devices, which may use a cookie, pixel or other similar technology placed by
Ubiz or the third party (although we would not share any other information that identifies you with an advertiser).
This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Ubiz and its service providers and does not cover the use of
cookies by any advertisers.
Your Ubiz account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent
unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately,
and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.
Ubiz endeavors to safeguard user information to ensure that user account information is kept private. However,
Ubiz cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software
failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.
The Services may contain links to other sites. Ubiz is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on
other sites. When linking to another site, you should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This Privacy Policy
only governs information collected on the Services.
International Users
If you are located outside of the United States, please note that this site is hosted on our computer servers in the
United States. Therefore, your information may be processed and stored in the United States. As a result, United
States federal and state governments, courts, or law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to obtain
disclosure of your information through laws applicable in the United States. Your use of the Sites or the Services
or your submission of any Personal Information to us will constitute your consent to the transfer of your Personal
Information outside of your home country, including the United States, which may provide for different data
protection rules than in your country.
Personal Information Can I Access
Ubiz allows you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations,
updating that information and ensuring that it is accurate and complete. This list will change as our Service changes.
•         Password
•         Phone number
•         Email address
•         Other User profile information (for example, home city, photo)
•         Usage information (for example, check-in history)

Information Removed
Even after you remove information from your account or profile, copies of that information may remain viewable
elsewhere, to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your privacy
settings, or it was copied or stored by other users. Removed and deleted information may remain on backup media
for up to ninety (90) days prior to being deleted from our servers.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
Ubiz may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy
Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make material changes in the way we use Personal
Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Services or sending you an email. Users are
bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when they use the Services after such changes have been first posted.
